本 字 幕 由 隨 緣 字 幕 組 修 訂 製作
歡迎 加 群 374282202 一起 看 片 ◑ ω ◑
字 幕 轉 制 ｜ 天 外 生物
感謝 原 字 幕 製作 者
- 生日 快樂 ！ - 來 吃 蛋糕
- Happy Birthday! - Hey, birthday cake!
- 我 來了 - 謝謝
- There I am. - Thank you.
- 味道 不錯 - 等一下 有 人 要 這個 嗎
- That's nice! - Wait, everybody wants this?
當 你 出於 同情 邀請 人來 參加 生日 宴 就 會 這樣
That's what happens when you do a mercy invite.
我 相信 你 盡力 請了 所有 人
I believe you manage to invite everyone.
爸爸 我 不能 邀請 班 裡 所有 人
Dad, I can't invite everyone in my art class, except for one person
但 忽略 她 這 一個 沒有 任何 社 交 圈 的 人 我 不想 讓 她 再 多 心
without social networking evidence, inflicting more pain on that person wasn't intended.
- 我 又 不是 怪物 - 我 為 你 驕傲 我 想
- And I'm not a monster. - I'm proud of you, I think.
她 經常 被 留 堂 有 時候 她 會對 老師 大喊大叫
She gets detention a lot, and she yells at teacher sometimes.
還有 傳言 說 他 經常 離家 出 走
And there was a rumor that went around that she just kept running from home.
- 也許 她 能 自己 叫 " 優 步 " - 我 真 覺得 我們 可以 回家 了
- Maybe she can UBER. - I seriously believe that we can go home now.
什麼 時候 輪到 你們 民 主 決定 了 ？
Did I mistakenly convey this is a democracy?
等到 有 人 接 她 我們 再 走
We are not going until she gets picked up.
車 壞了
The car broke down.
- 我 坐 公 交 回去 - 你 不用 坐 公 交
- I'm just gonna take the bus. - You're not taking a bus.
我 送 你 回去
I'll drive you home
克 萊 爾 差不多 存 了 將近 一半 的 買 車 錢
Claire has almost saved her half of the money she needs for her car.
是 吧 ？
Isn't that right?
至少 這 是 我 為 數 不多 能 開 車 帶 你們 兜 風 的 機會
At least it'll be one of a few times left that I can drive you guys around.
你 要是 不來 就 沒 機會 聽我 爸
You won't be able to hear my Dad tell jokes that only he thinks
全 程 說 只有 他 自己 覺得 好笑 的 冷笑 話 了
are funny for an entire car ride, unless you come.
你 不會 想 錯過 這個 的
You don't really wanna miss that.
哇 噢 我 收 到 的 禮物 比 想 象 中 還 多 唉
Wow, I got more gifts than I thought you did.
放 這 兒 行 嗎
Can I put this in here?
行 放 著 我 來吧 謝謝你 瑪西亞
Yeah, yeah, I'll get it. Thank you, Marcia.
也許 他 只是
Maybe he's just...
也許 他 只是 假裝 擔心
Maybe he's just pretend to worry.
有 什麼 事 嗎 ？
Can I help you?
什麼 ？
What?
就是 這個 人 他 特別 有 趣
This is the one he's so, he's really funny.
他 負責 這個 周 播 視 頻
He does this weekly video.
等一下 這 也 太 隨意 了 吧 好奇 怪
Wait a minute. That's so random. So weird.
你 看 他的 好 評 我 不明 白 為 什麼
You look praise on him. I don't get it.
- 你 為 什麼 搞 不懂 啊 - 我 就是 想 不通 啊
- Post it! Why don't you get it? - I just don't get it.
- 他 很 可愛 呀 - 哪有 他的 眉毛 就 像 ...
- He is cute. - No, his eyebrows are just like..
- 噢 萌 到 你 了 是 吧 - 好吧 是 挺 有 趣 的
- Yeah! That gets you! - Okay, that's funny, yeah.
- 你 看到 他 怎麼 做到 的 嗎 - 他 怎麼會 那樣 做
- You see how he does that? - How does he even do that?
- 等等 我 幹 嘛 要 讓 你 看 啊 - 看 啊 對
- Wa.. wait, why I let you see it. - Watching, yes!
這 也 太 壞了
This is so bad!
嘿
Hey!
不好意思 先生 你 上 錯 車 了 吧
Pardon me, Sir. I think you have the wrong car.
分裂
我們 醒來 就 在 這 了
We woke up in here.
發生 什麼 了
What the hell is going on?
我們 在 這 幹 嘛 我 爸 出 什麼 事 了
What are we doing here? What happened to my dad?
他 就 在 外面
He's out there.
你 知道 我 爸 出 什麼 事 了 ？
Do you know what happened to my dad?
我 決定 讓 你 先來
I choose you first.
很快 就 好
It's only gonna be a minute.
尿 褲子 尿 褲子
Pee on yourself. Pee on yourself.
不 不要
No! No!
不
No!
不要
Don't!
No!
開門
Open the door!
有 我 在 呢 你 還好 嗎
I'm here, okay? Are you okay?
他 要 我 給 他 跳舞
He wanted me dance for him.
外面 那 道 門鎖 起來 了
The outer door is locked.
沒事 的
Everything is okay.
我們 會 沒事 的
We're okay.
沒事
我 聽見 渺小 靈魂 飛 濺 的 聲音
I hear the tiny soul splashed.
然後 他 過來 了 一個 怪物 就 像這 樣
And here it comes, a freak of nature, like this,
他 淌 過 小溪
so he comes across the stream.
他 太 高 了 溪水 都 沒 不 到 他的 肚子
And he's so tall, that the water doesn't even get to his belly.
接着 他 停下 了 我 心 都 快 跳到 嗓 子 眼 了
Then he stops. My heart's coming out of my chest.
你 腦 子 燒 壞了 約翰 叔叔 腦 子 燒 壞了
You got bug fever. Uncle John's got bug fever.
不是 這樣 的 凱 西 你 爸爸 說謊
That's not true, Casey. Your dad is a liar.
- 攔 魚網 架 多大 - 超 大
- How big was the rack? - It was huge!
他 應該 注意 哪裏 呢 凱 西
Where is supposed to look on, Casey?
- 身體 那 為 什麼 他 看 的 是 攔 魚網 架 - 因 為 他 腦 子 燒 壞了
- At the body. And why is he looking at the rack? - 'Cause he got bug fever.
你 說什 麼 她 都 同意
She'll say anything you've said.
等 你 三年 內 拿到 指導 狩獵 許可 證 你 會 這麼 做 嗎
Are you gonna do that when you got your mentored hunting license in 3 years?
不會 啊
No, Sir.
吃完 記得 把 手 套 戴上
Be sure you put your gloves on after you finish.
剛 出去 手腳 會 冷
Your feet and your hands get cold first out there.
三 名 學生 遭 綁架 其中 一人 的 父親
Three students abducted. The father of one of the students
在 普 魯 士 國王 商 場 從 昏迷 中 醒來
woke up daze from in King of Prussia,
據 報 道 是 被 下了 迷 藥 他 發現 孩子 和 車 都 不 見 了
reportedly drugged, he found the kids and the car missing.
附近 居民 均 感到 震驚
Neighbors are in disbelief.
事件 發生 後 仍 無 訊息
A normally quiet convenient is real after the savage.
如果 你 有 任何 這些 女孩 離 奇 失 蹤 的 訊息
If you any information concerning these girls you are heard,
請 聯 繫 警 方
please contact the police.
我 要 見你 立刻
" Barry S:I need to see you. Urgent. "
你 能不能 開啟 那 扇 門 都 沒用 的 克 萊 爾
Doesn't matter if you open that door, Claire.
還有 一扇 鎖 著 的 門
There is a second locked door.
他 還會 來 的 這 一次
He's gonna come in here again. And his second in,
我們 絕不 讓 他 再 帶走 誰 了
we're not letting him take one of us out again.
我們 只 知道 哭喊
We just gridded and screamed.
我們 沒 傷到 他 是 因 為 我們 不敢 讓 他 不 高興
We didn't hurt him because we were afraid to get him upset.
天 吶 這些 受害者 的 事 天 吶
God, that's victim's shit! Jesus!
我們 要 反抗 我們 應該 狠狠 回 擊 他
We should fight him. We should drop a crazy ass balm on him.
我 看 他 輕輕 鬆 鬆 就 能 把 你們 抓 出去 丟 在 床 上
I saw him carried one of you and laid you in the bed like you had nothing.
就算 跟 他 動 手 我們 也 出 不去
Punching him would not gonna help us out.
我 上了 ... 上了 六個月 的 空手 道 課 程
I took, I took six months of kempo karate class.
你 假裝 不 舒服 讓 他 分心
And you distract him with pain.
你們 覺得 什麼 都 很 容易 ？
Everything is so easy for you guys.
你 稍微 有 個 舉動 他 都 能 猜 到 你 要 做什麼
You do one thing, he can predict the next thing.
這 種 情況 下 我們 不該 這麼 做
It's not the way it's gonna be in this situation.
你 是說 我們 根本 出 不去 了
We're not getting out of here! You're saying,
你 是 打算 放棄 一切 抵抗 是嗎
you're not gonna fight with everything in you?
你 要 知道 唯 一 的 機會
You know, the only chance..
我們 唯 一 的 機會
The only chance we have..
是 我們 三個 一起 盡全力 攻擊 他
is if all three of us go crazy on this guy.
我們 得 快點 了
We have to hurry.
我們 需要 你 凱 西
We need you, Casey.
克 萊 爾 很 聰明 就 聽 她 的 吧
Claire is smart, let's listen to her.
你 上 我 也 上
I'll do it if you're gonna do it, too.
- 我們 能 打過 他 - 他 會 傷到 我們
- We can win. - He'll hurt us.
行了 閉嘴 吧 你們 兩 個 ...
Now, shut up, both of you.
你 要 振作起來 別 這麼 悲 觀 幫 咱 們一 起 逃出去
You're gonna pick your miserable self up and help us get out of here.
唬 我 ？
Blow me.
你 在 普 魯 士 國王 商 場 上 的 六個月 空手 道 課 也能 唬 到 我 ？
And your 6 months of karate at the King of Prussia Mall can blow me, too.
你 今天 不能 這樣 你 現在 不能 這樣
No, no, you can't do this today! You can't do this right now!
你 為 什麼 要說 這 話 為 什麼 表現 成 這樣
Why are you do this! Why are you act like this?
爲 什麼 好像 你 跟 我們 不是 一夥 的
Why do act like you're not one of us?
你 瞄準 的 時候 凱 西
When you aiming Casey...
要 讓 兩隻 眼睛 都 睜開
Always keep both eyes open.
用 槍 管 瞄準 你的 目標 隨 著 它 移動 不要 跟 丟了
Cover your target with the barrel, then move with it. To get its pase.
我 得說 第一次 拿 槍 都 很難
I am warning you its gonna be hard first times.
要 麼 會 太近 要 麼 會 太遠
You are gonna shoot under or behind it.
你 要 儘量 角度 合適
You will earn to stay with it.
雌 性 比 雄性 聰明 你 知道 的 就 像 人 一樣
Females are smarter than the males. But you know that, its like humans.
雌 性 靠 嗅 覺 求生 確保 自己 有 掩 護
Females use their nose to stay alive. And make sure they have cover.
時刻 記住 他們 無時無刻 不 在 求生
And always remember, they are trying to stay alive.
雄鹿 平時 單獨 行動 交配 季節 群 聚
Bucks, go off by them selves. Bucks get down during laiding season.
男孩 總是 吵 吵鬧 鬧 的
Boys makes too much noise.
是 啊 沒錯
Yes they do.
我 比 男孩 優秀 對 吧
I'm better than a boy, right?
是 的 沒錯
Yes you are.
我 聽到 什麼 有 用 的 會 告訴 你們 的
I'll let you know when I hear something that makes sense.
我們 都 不知道 現在 什麼 情況
We don't even know what this is yet.
我 有 了 靈感
I was inspired.
不 不 ... 是 那 張 粉 色 法 爾 可 前面 那 張
No, no, that one, before the pink fraco,
那 應該是 件 ... 像 西 裝 外 套 的 衣服
That supposed to be like a.. Like a tailored jacket..
但是 我 會 把 她 捧 上 報 紙 頭 條 的
But I'm gonna himp her with newspaper headlines.
我 一般 只 穿 寬 鬆 簡單 的 襯衫 和 裙子 但是 這些
Well, I'm a simple blouse and skirt person, but these..
這些 很有 藝 術 感 巴 里
These are very artistic, Barry.
就是 那 種 住 漢 斯 頓 斯 的 女人 們 願意 一萬 五千 美 元 買來
Just the kinda thing Hamptons'ladies would spend 15000 dollars on
只 為 在 慈 善 舞 會上 穿上 一次
to wear once at a charity ball.
閉嘴 啦 你 知道 我 待 不了 太 久
Shut up! You know, I can't stay too long.
我 就是 來 看看 你
This is just a visit.
好吧 跟 我 說說 發生 了 些 什麼
Well, tell me what's going on?
什麼 你 是說 郵 件 嗎
What? You mean the email?
就是 一封 平常 的 郵 件 呀 我 就是 壓力 有 點 大
It's just the usual thing. Just feeling a bit overwhelmed.
看 你的 郵 件 感覺 有 特殊 情況 而且 時間 緊 迫
Your email made it sounds specific and time related.
- 你 在 找 什麼 嗎 - 沒 啊 我 就是 看看
- Are, are you looking for something? - No. I'm just admiring.
- 我 現在 好多 了 - 工作 怎麼樣
- I'm better now. - How's work?
- 很好 啊 - 我 上次 和 他們 聊 的 時候
- Great! - When I last spoke to them,
他們 認 為 你 是個 模範 員 工
they believe you were a model employee.
他們 覺得 你 是個 一絲 不 苟 有 責任 心 的 人
They found you meticulous and conscientious.
- 你 知道 的 對 吧 - 我 知道
- You know this, right? - I do.
你 在 那裏 工作 快 十年 了 你 做得 很 棒 巴 里
You've managed there for 10 years. It's functioning very well, Barry.
而且 像 那樣 適合 你的 工作 環境 很少
And it's a rare and wonderful place for you to work.
是 的
Yes it is.
你 知道 我 這 邊 類似 於 你 這 種 病人 中 只有 你 在 工作 方面 是 最 穩 定 的
You know, of all my other clientswith your disorder, you've been the most consistent at your job.
出 什麼 事情 了 嗎 巴 里
Did something happen, Barry?
你 多大 了 ？
How old are you?
在 網上 查到 的 資訊 似乎 不太 準
The internet isn't consistent on this point.
你 在 想 什麼 呢
Why is that on your mind?
你 退休 或者 去世 之後 誰 來 照顧 你 呢
Who's gonna look after you when you retired or passed on?
你 懂得 我們 得 照顧 自己 而且 那 時 人們 甚至 會 無視 你的 存 在
You know, we're gonna have to take care of ourselves and nobody even believes that we exist.
如果 我 有 發生 什麼不 測 我 已經 做了 安排
If ever something would happened to me,
一個 巴 爾 的 摩 的 同 事 會 幫 我 處理 後 事
I've made arrangements with a colleague from Baltimore to take over.
嘿 你 ... 一個人 住 嗎
Hey, you a.. you live alone?
- 你 明知 道 - 抱 歉 我 是 問 多久 了
- You know this. - I'm sorry, I just meant how long?
一直 如此
Always.
那一 定 很 孤 單 吧
That must be so lonely.
你 知道 的 我 已經 好多 了 我 不應該 給 你 發 郵 件 的
You know what, I'm.. I'm doing much better. I shouldn't have emailed you.
我 只是 ... 你 也看 到了 我 太 沖 動 了
I'm just.. Look at me, I'm too impulsive.
對了 ... 有 人 在 關注 我 的 病情 嗎 有 人 關注 我們 的 治療 嗎
By the way, is anybody listening? Does anybody care about us?
有 的 其實 巴 黎 大 學 讓 我 去 做 一個 演 講
Yes, the University of Paris asked me to do a lecture, in fact.
我 會 通過 網 絡 電 話 就 在 這裏 來 做 演 講
I'm going to be doing it via Skype, from right here.
關注 的 人 越來越 多 了
People are believing more.
我們 下 週 還 是 老 時間 再見 吧
Let's meet at our usual time next week.
你 先 別 走 巴 里
I'd rather you didn't leave, Barry.
出 什麼 事情 了 嗎
Did something happen?
沒事 啦 我 就是 來 看看 你 我 現在 好多 了
Don't worry, this was just a visit. I'm doing much better.
那 你的 草 圖 是 怎麼回事 巴 里
And what's with your sketches, Barry?
你 一直 都 很 保護 它們 的
You're usually very protective of them.
是 啊 謝謝
Yeah, thanks.
我 下 週 老 時間 再來 找 你
I'll see you next week at our usual time.
謝謝你 為 我們 作 鬥爭 弗 萊 徹 醫生
Thanks for fighting for us, Dr. Fletcher.
- 謝謝 弗 萊 徹 醫生 - 不用 謝
- Thanks, Dr. Fletcher. - You're welcome.
- 我 覺得 我 會 搞 砸 的 - 不會 的 一切 都 會 很 棒 的
- I just think I'm gonna blow it. - No, it would be great.
- 下 週 見 - 謝謝
- I'll see you next week. - Okay, thank you.
我 不知道 你 怎麼 和 那些 人相 處 的
I don't know how you work with those people.
- 和 哪些 人 ？ - 你的 病人 們
- With what people? - Your patients.
你 不能 用你 的 大拇指 去 轉 輪子 ... 蠢貨
You can't use your thumbs to spin the wheel, dumb asses!
他們 總是 用 大拇指
They always use their thumbs!
我們 看 的 病人 都是 受過 挫折 被 視 為 異類 的 不 健全 人
Well, we look at people who've been shattered and different as less than,
但 如果 其實 ... 他們 比 我們 還 健全 呢
What if, they are more than us?
什麼 ？
What?
你 相信 他們 嗎 你的 病人 們
You believe them? Your patients?
你 懂得 啦 就 你 我 之間 說說
You know, just between you and me.
是 的 我 信
Yes, I do.
別 停 在 這 快 彈 開
Flick it! Flick it!
無意 冒犯 但是 我 不信
I don't believe it. No offense.
那個 我 要 買 那個
That! I need to buy that.
- 他 回來 了 - 有 個 女人 在 外面
- He's back. - There is a lady outside.
- 丹 尼斯 快 說你 做了 些 什麼 - 你 別 生氣
- Dennis, admit what you've done. - Don't get upset.
放下 我 已經 嚇 到了
Take down, I'm getting frightened.
我 以 為 你 能 控制 住
I thought that you had this under control.
- 快 告訴 我 現在 還 來得及 - 食物 正 等着 呢
- Please tell me it's not too late. - The food in the waiting.
她 在 那個 房間 嗎
Is she in that room?
- 我們 在 這裏 - 救命
- We are here! - Help us!
我們 在 這裏 ！
We are here!
- 我 的 天 有 幾個 人 - 不 別 進去
- Jesus, how many are they? - No, no, don't go in there!
別 進去
Don't go in there!
不要 擔心 。
Don't worry.
我 會 和 他 談談 的 他 聽我 的話
I'll talk to him. He listens to me.
他 狀態 不好
He's not well.
他 知道 你們 為 什麼 在 這 兒
He knows what you're here for.
我 不會 允許 他 碰 你們 的
He's not allowed to touch you.
他 知道 的
He knows that.
- 凱 倫 - 喬
- Karen. - Joe.
他們 說 你 在 全國 性 會議 上有 單獨 的 發言 時間
They said you can have your own part at the national conference.
他們 做出 了 讓步
They conceded, however,
我 可以 參與 心 境 障礙 模 式 的 部分
I can be part of the mood disorder pattern.
- 那 不是 心 境 障礙 - 我 知道 你 堅持 的 觀點 凱 倫
- It's not a mood disorder. - I'm aware your beliefs, Karen.
他們 這 次會 公開 新 證據 嗎
Well, were they open this time with a new evidence?
你的 論點 之一 是 一隻 狗
One of your arguments is a dog.
你 提 交了 一隻 狗 的 視 頻
You submitted video of a dog
講 的 是 它 在 不同 時間 對 你 病人 的 不同 反應
acting differently to one of your patients at different time.
事實 更加 戲 劇 化
It is more dramatic than that.
每一 個人 格 都 堅信 自身 的 存 在
They are what they believe they are.
他的 大 腦 學會 了 捍 衛 自己
The brain has learned to defend itself.
你 這麼 對待 他們 就 好像 他們 有 超自然 天賦 似 的
You treated them like they're supernaturally gifted.
好像 他們 有 超 能力 還 是 別 的 什麼
Like they have powers or something.
凱 倫 他們 是 病人 他們 經歷過 創傷
Karen, these are patients. They have been to trauma.
也許 他們 能做 到 我們 做 不 到 的 事情
And perhaps now they're capable of something we're not.
我們 現在 有 腦 部 掃 描
We have brain scans now.
多 重 人 格 的 病人 們 能夠 隨 著 他們 的 想法 改變 體內 的 化 學 反應
DID patients have changed their body chemistry with their thoughts.
他 剛剛 就是 想 嚇 我們
He was just trying to scare us.
他 在 自言自語 說 些 傻 話
He was making a fool conversation with himself.
食物 正 等着 呢 那 句話 是 什麼 意思
What was that line about the food is waiting?
每個 出去 的 人 都 會 精神 失 常 嗎
Does everyone get out whacked?
我們 現在 就 要 逃出去
Just listen, we need to get out of here now.
不
Yeah, no, please.
拜 託 把 你們 的 地方 弄 乾淨 浴 室 這樣 我 不能 接受
Keep your area neat. The bathroom is unacceptable.
我 簡單 說 下 我 給 這些 起 個 代號
I'll make it easy. I, I've called a code of this.
藍色 的 瓶子 用來 擦 地板
Use the blue bottle for the floor.
粉 色 瓶子 擦 瓷 磚
And the pink bottle for ceramic surfaces.
帕 特 麗 夏 提醒 我
Patricia has reminded me that..
我 是 來 告訴 你們
I was sent to get you for a reason.
你們 是 些 受 驚 了 的 食物
That you are sacred food.
我 保證 我 不會 再來 煩 你們 了
And I promise not to bother you again.
也許 他 有 隻狗 或者 別 的 什麼 ？
Maybe he has a dog or something.
我 覺得 他 要 把 我們 喂 狗
I think he's gonna feed us to his dogs.
凱 西
Casey.
Casey!
我 叫 海 德 薇 格 我 有 紅 襪 子
My name is Hedwig. I have red socks.
他 要 來了
He's on the move.
什麼 ？
What?
他 要 來 了
He's on the move.
- 誰 ？ - 要 抓 你們 的 人 呀
- Who? - Someone who's coming for you.
你們 不會 喜歡 他的
And you're not gonna like it.
你 睡着 的 時候 你的 夥伴 們 鬧 了 一會兒
You guys make noises in your sleep.
- 告訴 我們 - 我 不應該 說 的
- Tell us. - I'm not supposed to say.
但是 他 對 別人 做 過 很 壞 的 事
Hmm.. But, he's done awful things to people.
而且 他 也會 對 你 做 很 壞 的 事
And he'll do awful things to you.
- 我 也有 藍色 的 短 襪 - 他的 食物 ？
- I have blue socks, too. - His food?
- 你 幾 歲 了 - 九 歲
- How old are you? - Nine.
這麼 說 你 不是 劫 持 我們 的 那個 傢伙 ？
So you're not the guy that took us?
- 不是 - 你 也不 是 那位 女士 ？
- No. - You're not the lady?
你 是 瞎了 嗎
What are you blind?
你 不知道 他們 在 想 什麼 嗎 ？
You don't know how they think?
不 他們 沒有 他們 沒有 告訴 我 太多 事
No, they don't, they don't tell me much.
我 只吃 了 一個 熱 狗
I just ate a hotdog.
你 能 救救 我們 嗎 海 德 薇 格
Could you help us, Hedwig?
不行 我 我 都 不應該 出現 在 這裏 的
No. I'm, I'm not even supposed to be here.
我 偷了 屬於 丹 尼斯 先生 的 時間
I stole a light from Mr. Dennis, but he'll be back real soon.
他 很快 就 會 回來 的 我 不能 出來 太 久 不然 他 就 會 發現 然後 非常 生氣
I can't steal a light for too long or he'll know and get angry, etc.
- 再見 - 等等
- See you! - Wait!
我們 聽說 了 一些 事
We heard something.
以前 我們 還不 懂 可 現在 我們 懂 了
We didn't understand it, but now we do.
- 你 知道 我們 聽到 了 什麼 嗎 - 你們 聽到 了 什麼
- Do you know what we heard? - What did you hear?
跟 我 來
Come here.
我 悄悄 說給 你 聽
I'll whisper it to you.
好
Okay.
這個 傢伙
This guy..
是 衝 著 你 來 的
is coming for you.
- 你 是個 大 騙子 - 我 從不 騙人 海 德 薇 格
- You're a big liar. - I never lie, Hedwig.
但是 但是 丹 尼斯 先生
But, but Mr. Dennis..
他 說過 他 跟蹤 了 那 兩 個 姑娘 四天
He said that he followed those two girls for four days.
而且 他 知道 她們 就是 他 要 找 的 人
And that he knew, that they were the ones that he would want.
你 不 在 的 時候 丹 尼斯 和 那位 女士 說過
When you're not around, Dennis and the lady talked about it.
他們 還說 了 這 次 他 有 多 想要 一個 男孩子
They talked about how he wants a boy this time.
他們 要 把 他 給 你
They're going to give him you.
不 帕 特 麗 夏 夫人 她 說過
No, Mrs. Patricia, she said...
她 說 她 根本 不生 我 的 氣
She said, she's not mad at me anymore.
她 有 時候 會 唱歌 給 我 聽
She sings to me sometimes.
我 覺得 帕 特 麗 夏 夫人 還 是有 點 生 你的 氣
I think Mrs. Patricia still a little mad at you.
帕 特 麗 夏 夫人 認 為 我 她 認 為 我 很 笨
Mrs. Patricia thinks I'm.. She thinks I'm stupid.
她 覺得 我 總 犯 低 級 錯誤
She thinks I made silly mistakes.
看 著 我 我們 就 像 你的 保姆
Look at me, we're like your babysitters.
我 會 給 你 看 電視 還要 給 你 做 美味 的 晚餐
I'll let you watch TV and make you a fun diner.
我們 都 需要 離開 這裏
We all need to get out of here.
你 可以 告訴 我 離開 的 路
You could show us the way out.
那樣 我們 就 可以 在 其他 人 回來 之前 離開 這裏
We can be out before anybody gets back.
我們 得 快點 海 德 薇 格
But we have to hurry, Hedwig.
我們 要 快點 行動 然後 離開 這裏
We have to hurry and get out of here.
等等 等一下
Wait, wait a minute.
我 花了 很大 力氣 才 讓 這個 地方 這麼 安全 沒人 打擾
It took forever to get this place safe without anybody to work here.
你 休想 從 這 出去 我 花了 很大 力氣 才 讓 這個 地方 這麼 安全 沒人 打擾
You can't get out of here! It took forever to get this place safe without anybody to work here.
你 休想 從 這 出去
You can't get out of here!
- 我 要 去 擤 鼻 涕 了 - 不 不 別 走 求 你 了
- I have to blow my nose. - No, no, please do not go!
誰 來了
Who's coming?
- 這 太 嚇 人 了 - 誰 也沒 來
- This is seriously scary. - No one is coming.
他 說了 些 什麼
He said something.
他 說了 一些 關於 讓 這個 地方 變 安全 的話
He said something about making the room safe.
這些 幹 板 牆 全是 新 的
This is all new drywall.
它 並不 安全
It wasn't safe.
等等 我們 知道 他 會 注意到 這個
Wait a minute, we know he'll notice about this?
凱 西 你 說得 對 這裏 確實 有 問題
Casey, you're right. There's something in here.
他 肯定 把 出路 堵 死了 他 來了 馬上 告訴 我
He must covering up the way out. Tell me if you see him.
凱 西 告訴 我 你 看見 什麼 了
Casey, tell us what you see!
他 來了
He's here.
不能 讓 他 進來 這 是 我們 唯 一 的 機會
You can't let him in, you can't let him in! This is our one chance.
- 我們 做 不 到 的 - 不 我們 會 的
- We're not gonna make it. - Yes, we are!
嘿 你們 幾個 在 幹 什麼
Wha.. Hey, what are you guys doing?
好了 別 鬧 了 嘿 夥 計 們
Okay, quit it. Hey guys!
- 讓 我 進去 - 等 一 小 會 兒 我們 在 換 衣服
- Let me in. - Give us a second, we are changing.
你們 到底 在 幹 什麼 呀
What are you guys doing?
讓 我 進去
Let me in!
你們 這 就 不好 玩 了
Guys, you're not being funny.
你們 現在 變成 壞 女孩 兒 了
You're being a bitch now.
- 我 要 ... - 攔住 他 能 攔 多久 攔 多久
- I'm gonna... - Just keep him there as long as you can.
你們 這樣 做 是 在 給 我 找麻煩
You're gonna get me in trouble.
小心
Watch out.
我 還 以 為 我 把 你 給 丟了
I thought I lost you.
你 能 出來 嗎
Would you step outside, please?
你 喜歡 戲弄 我們
You like to make fun of us.
可是 我們 比你 們 想 象 的 強大 多 了
But, we're more powerful than you think.
出來
Step outside.
請 出來
Please.
你 不應該 戲弄 孩子 的
You shouldn't trick children.
這 讓 我 看清楚 了 你 是 什麼樣 的 人
That shows who you are.
看看 你的 毛衣 全 毀了 太 髒 了
Look at your sweater. It's ruined, it's dirty.
脫下 來
Remove it.
我 在 努力 跟 你 客 氣
I'm trying to be good.
你們 再也 不會 見到 你的 朋友 了
You'll not see your friend again.
她 會 被 單獨 關押
She'll be kept separate.
現在 你 還有 你 把 上衣 都 脫了
Now, take off your skirt and take off your shirt.
那些 塵土 把 你們 全 弄髒 了
Because you got all dirty from the dust.
一個 罹 患 分離 性 身 份 識 別 障礙 的 患者
One identity in an individual with Dissociative Identity Disorder
他的 一個人 格 會 存 在 高 膽 固 醇 的 問題 只有 一個
Can have high cholesterol. One.
有 過 這樣 的 案 例 一個人 格 對 蜜蜂 的 叮 咬 過 敏 而 另一 個人 格 則 不會
There are been cases where one identity is allergic to bee stings. The others are not.
有 沒有 這樣 的 可能 兩 個人 格 會 同時 存 在
Are there moments where two identities can co-exist at the same time?
很多 時候 兩 個人 格 會 在 同 一時 間 出現 在 聚 光 燈 之下
There are times when two identities
或者是 有 意識
can take the light or the spot, or consciousness at the same time.
一個 和 我 共 事 的 學生 身上 發生 過 這 種 情況
This happened with a student that I was working with.
在 同 一時 間 她 的 左右手
And her left and right hands were taking notes
會 用 不同 的 字 體 來 記 筆 記 而且 是 分別 記錄 不同 的 內容
in different hand-writings about separate things at the same time.
不同 人 格 之間 的 差 異 可以說是 非常 具有 戲 劇 性 的
The differences in the identities can be dramatic.
你 我 之間 有 多麼 不同
As much as the difference between you and me,
在 場 的 觀 眾 有 多 不同 那些 人 格 就 有 多 不同
and every person in that auditorium.
不同 的 人 格 會有 不同 的 智 商
The identities have different IQs.
身體 素 質 也 各不相同
They have different physical strengths.
一種 人 格 是 俄 羅斯 舉 重 運動員
One personality is a Russian weightlifter,
能夠 舉起 比 自己 體 重 沉 三 倍 的 東西
and can lift three times of his body weight.
他們 精神 高度 集中
Their ability to hyper-focus and have
和 經歷 不同 事情 的 能力 是非 常 驚人 的
different experiences is astounding.
是 不是 這個 群 體 的 人 通過 自身 的 遭遇
Have these individuals through their suffering
開 發了 人類 大 腦 更大 的 潛 能
unlocked the potential of the brain?
這 是 不是 就是 我們
Is this the ultimate doorway
去 探索 未 知 事物 的 終 極 途徑
to all things we called unknown?
這 是 不是 就是 很多 我們 認識 到 的 超自然 現 象 的 起 因
Is this where our sense of the supernatural comes from?
那 關於 深 度 和 ...
It's about depth and a..
一條 曲 線 還有 ...
and curves. And, hey, you see that one?
嘿 你 看見 那個 了 嗎 就 像 一件 又 舊 又 汗 溼 的 衣服
It's kinda like a senile sweaty dress.
你 是誰 ？
Who are you?
巴 里
Barry.
我 覺得 你 不是
I don't think you are.
我 現在 已經 練 出來 分辨 誰 在 跟 我 說話 誰 沒 跟 我 說話 的 本事 了
I've developed a nose for sensing whom I'm talking to and whom I'm not.
我 做了 什麼 事 嗎
Have I done something?
你 連續 兩天 發 郵 件 ... 想要 在 沒有 預 約 的 情況 下 和 我 見面
You've emailed for an unscheduled appointment two days in a row.
我 就是 覺得 我 被 其他 人 格 壓制 住 了 我 出了 一些 問題
I just feel overwhelmed, I've gotten some issues.
我 認 為 奧 威 爾 或者 傑 德 或者 塞 繆 爾 或者 海 因 裡 希
I think Orwell, or Jade, or Samuel..
主 導 了 一會兒 給 我 發了 郵 件
Or Heinrich had the light for a moment and emailed me.
你 卻 在 這裏 告訴 我 一切 都 好
And you're here to tell me everything is okay.
是 我 給 你 發 的 郵 件
I emailed you.
我 能不能 和 他們 其中 一個 說話
May I talk to one of them, please?
那是 不可能 的
That can't happen.
我 告訴 過 他們 今天 你 要 給 我 進行 治療
I told them that I wanna spend the session with you today.
我 再 問你 一遍 我 現在 到底 在 和 誰 交談
I'm gonna ask again. To whom am I speaking with now?
弗 萊 徹 博士 我 是 巴 里 啊
Dr. Fletcher, it's Barry.
你 看起來 不是 巴 里 巴 里 該 是個 外向 型 的 領導者
It doesn't seem like Barry. Barry is an extroverted leader.
我 當然是 這樣 啊
Of course, I am.
讓 我 這 專業 人 士 來 猜 一 猜
I'm gonna take a professional guess.
我 是 根據 巴 里 告訴 我 的 猜 的 他 對 凱 文 身體 裡
Based on the description of all 23 identities that live in Kevin's body,
住 著 的 所有 二十 三種 人 格 進行 了 詳細 的 描述
that I've gotten from Barry.
我 想 我 是 在 和 丹 尼斯 交談
I think, I'm talking to Dennis.
但是 他 因 為 些 其他 的 原因 被 弄得 見 不得 人 了
But he's been banned from the light because among other reasons.
他的 癖好 是 觀看 年輕 姑娘 裸體 跳舞
He has a proclivity to watch young girls dance naked,
他 自己 也 知道 這樣 不對 他 努力 克 服 這個 缺點 並且 小 有 進步
which he himself knows it's wrong. And he's fought against it with a little success.
我 很 開心 我們 終於 見面 了
I'm encouraged we can finally meet.
我 做出 這樣 的 猜測 是 因 為 你 自從 來到 這裏 之後 就 動 手 擺 了 巧 克 力 盤 兩次
And I guess this because you've adjusted the chocolate dish twice.
而且 我 知道 你 患有 強迫 症
since you came in here and I understand you have OCD.
我 明白 了 我 明白 了 真是 聰明
Now I see, now I see. That's clever.
- 可 我 不是 丹 尼斯 - 還有 你 和 帕 特 麗 夏 被 禁止 出現
- But I'm not Dennis. - And you and Patricia..
已經 有 好 一陣子 了
have been banned from the light for quite a while now.
我們 可以 說 主要 是 你的 信念 造成 的
Primarily, shall we say because of your beliefs.
帕 特 麗 夏 和 丹 尼斯 非常 不穩 定
Patricia and Dennis are very unstable.
而 我 不是 丹 尼斯 你們 倆 都 拿到 控制 權 了 嗎
I'm not Dennis. Have you both take in charge now?
請 相信 我 我 就是 巴 里
Please believe me, I'm Barry.
你 得 原諒 我 我 的 工作 就是 要 挑戰 你
You must forgive me, my job is to challenge you.
你 現在 也 必須 得知 道
And as you must know by now,
我 心裏 有 很多 關於 每個人 應該 怎麼樣 過 好 自己 生活 的 意見
I have plenty of opinions about how everyone should live their lives.
問 我 些 關於 時 尚 的 問題 吧 我 能 證明 自己
Ask me something about fashion, I'll prove it.
或者 要 麼 你 ... 你 看看
Or.. Or you..
看看
Look, look, look.
你 看 我 不是 丹 尼斯 你 還想 讓 我 做什麼 證明
You see, I'm not Dennis. You want me to do something else?
你 有 冰 淇 淋 嗎 反正 這 件 襯衫 也是 混 棉 的
You got ice cream? This shirt is cotton blend anyway.
這 顏色 都是 三個 季節 之前 的 了 是 裸 色 的 沒 關係 來 試 吧
The color is from three seasons ago. It's nude, I mean, come on.
傑 伊 你 總是 準備 快 餐 食 品 真是 太 沒 健康 意識 了 這 是 你 之前 買 的 雞 翅 嗎
Jay, what health conscious fast food prepare Did you originally buy these chicken wings,
你 這麼 喜歡 給 它 重新 加 熱 簡直 是 慢性 自殺
you're so lovingly heated it in minor suicidal gesture?
貓頭鷹 運動 餐 廳 的 你 可以 直接 扔掉 弗 萊 徹 醫生
Hooters. You can't just threw them out, Dr. Fletcher.
這樣 看 好多 地方 都 不對
This is so wrong on so many levels. We finished about 3:15,
我們 在 三點 十五 分 結束 的 在 三點 十八 分 附近 找 一下
so look around 3:18.
中間 再 放 慢 點 傑 伊
You're getting a little softer on the middle, Jay.
貓頭鷹 運動 餐 廳 的 創始 人 利用 了 肥胖 人 士 的 需求
The authors of hooters play on that need for fat,
還 吸引 了 那些 渴望 接近 大 胸 妹 的 男人 們
and men to be in the proximity of augmented breasts.
就 像是 亨 利 五 世 開 一家 連 鎖 快 餐 店 一樣
It's like Henry the 5th running a fast food franchise.
- 是個 好 地方 弗 萊 徹 醫生 - 哼 哼 對 啊
- It's a good place, Dr. Fletcher. - Hmm.. right.
你 是 怎麼 知道 垃圾 會 溢位 來 的
How did you know the trash will be spilled?
我 該 怎麼 說 呢 傑 伊 你 不是 非常 拘 泥 小 節 的 那 種 人
How can I say this, Jay, you're not the most meticulous of people.
這個 人 走過 垃圾堆 的 時候 不是 那麼 利 索 啊
This guys isn't very neat as he walked right through the trash.
不 傑 伊 任何 正常 的 人 都 會 繞 過去 的
No, Jay. A normal person would've walked around that.
那是 故意 的 你的 目 的 是 什麼 丹 尼斯
That was an act. What are your object, Dennis?
難道 是 帕 特 麗 夏 在 支配 你 嗎
Or is it Patricia who deciding things?
我們 不會 死 的
We're not gonna die.
發生 過 壞事
Bad things happened.
但是 不應該 是 這樣 的
But not like this.
凱 西
Casey.
和 我 聊 聊 啊
Talk to me.
我們 得 找個 窗戶 或者 門 什麼 的 是 不是 啊
We need to get through a window or a door?
獵物 ... 凱 西 制 勝 的 關鍵 在於 你 能不能
The trail. Casey, it's about where you can or can't.
比 這 動物 聰明
You have to outsmart this animal.
你 過去 可不 是 很 喜歡 來 這裏 啊
So you didn't used to like to come out here.
這 就 像是 我們 家族 的 傳統 一樣 是 吧
This is like our family tradition, right?
打得 好 兄弟
Good shooting, Bro.
我 給 你 拿 飯 來了 小 懶 蟲
I have your meal, sleepyhead.
吃 吧
Eat.
好吃 嗎 裏面 放了 紅 辣 椒
It's good? It's got paprika in it.
對不起
I'm sorry.
我 覺得 我 該 在 你 頭髮 裡 插上 一朵 漂亮 的 花兒
I think I'll put a pretty flower in your hair.
太 棒 了
Oh, yeah.
這 是用 來 彰顯 你 有 多麼 的 重要
This is to show how important you are.
跟 我 來 我們 好好 吃 一頓 吧
Come along. And we'll have a proper meal.
我 明白 這 一切 你們 看起來 不是 很 滿意
I understand, these must all seem so unsatisfactory for you.
可是 我們 正在 盡力 改善 呀
But, we are doing the best we can.
不錯 吧
Good?
- 克 萊 爾 能 和 我們 一起 吃 嗎 - 不能 不 恐怕 那樣 不行
- Can Claire come eat with us? - No, I'm afraid that can't happen.
她 幾乎 毀掉 了 我們 盛大 的 招待 儀式
She almost ruined our big reception.
我 聽說 亞 洲 人 的 音樂 能 促進 消化
I've heard that Asian people's music helps digestion.
我 給 你們 再做 一個 三 明 治
I'll make you a second sandwich.
你們 知道 嗎
Do you know..
一家 子 獅子 一天 能 進食 三十五 英 鎊
How many of lions can eat 35 pounds a day?
昆蟲 在 交配 季節 互相 追逐 的 時候 可以 減輕 百分之 三十 的 體 重 嗎
A bug can loose 30% of its weight during mating season chasing those round?
他們 倆 日夜不停 嗎
That creep paskula, right?
音樂 在 日夜不停 的 播 放 對 你們 有 好處 的
Means they travel around during dask and dawn. Good for you.
切 彎 了
It's crooked.
請 原諒 我
Forgive me.
你們 知道 嗎 ... 老 虎
I don't know if you know, but..
只有 三十 顆 牙
Tigers have only 30 teeth.
比 狗 還 少 十二 顆
That's 12 less than a dog.
我 覺得 這個 小 知識 挺 有 意思
I thought that was a fun fact.
去 你的 房間 把 門 關上 現在 就 去
Go to your room, shut the door. Do it now.
在 陽光 下 我們 能 找到 我們 的 激情
" In the sun, we'll find our passion"
在 陽光 下 我們 能 找到 我們 的 目標
" In the sun, we will find our purpose"
你們 總是 被 保護 起來 沒有 真正 的 遭受 過 痛苦
You've always been protected, you've never truly suffered.
所以 我們 選擇 了 你 你 總是 處 在 睡 夢 之中
That's why we chose you. You've always been asleep.
你 有 過 一次 機會
You've had a chance.
你 從 未有 過 機會
You've never had a chance.
那個 黑 頭髮 的 女孩 她 得 關押 在 另外 一個 小 房間 裡 了
The dark-haired girl, she's gonna be kept in another closet.
我 知道 這 意味着 什麼
I might as well know what this point.
怪物 要 衝 著 你們 來了
The beast is coming for you. All three of you.
衝 著 你們 三個 你們 需要 分開 關押
You'll gonna be kept separate.
你 ... 你 衣服 上有 面 包 屑
You've got a crumb on your shirt.
請 把 它 脫下 來
Please take it off.
你 就 ... 把 它 脫掉 吧
Just.. just take it off.
你 說 帕 特 麗 夏 太太 的 壞話 可不 好
It wasn't nice what you said about Mrs. Patricia.
你 撒謊 了
You lied.
我 很 抱 歉 海 德 薇 格
I'm sorry about that, Hedwig.
你們 幾個 對 我 撒謊 嚇壞 了 我 ...
You guys lied to me, made me scare, etc.
丹 尼斯 說 你 會 穿 許多 件 襯衫
Mr. Dennis says you wear a lot of shirts.
我 喜歡 這 一件
I like this shirt.
謝謝你
Thank you.
你 知道 丹 尼斯 和 帕 特 麗 夏 太太 是誰 嗎
Do you know who Dennis and Mrs. Patricia are?
不
No.
你 看 我們 每個人 都 得 坐 在 椅子 上等 著
See, everyone of us has to wait in a chair.
而 巴 里 他 決心 要 佔據 主 導
And Barry, he decides to stand in the light.
但是 因 為 我 巴 里 失去 了 那個 能力
But Barry lost that power because of me.
我 只是 希望 自己 能夠 ... 能夠 一直 擁有 這 種 特殊 能力
I can wish myself in the light anytime I want with a special power.
只要 我 樂意 巴 里 就 只能 一直 坐 在 椅子 上 乾 等
And Barry just have to keep sitting in his chair, if I wanted to.
所以 丹 尼斯 和 帕 特 麗 夏 太太 說 我 可以 和 他們 待 在一起
That's why Dennis and Mrs. Patricia said I could be with them.
丹 尼斯 和 帕 特 麗 夏 太太 他們 都 相信 怪物 的 存 在
Dennis and Mrs. Patricia, they believe
還有 它 能做 到 的 事
in the beast and what it can do.
你 見過 他 嗎
Have you seen him?
那個 ... 怪物
The.. beast?
沒有 啊 我 可以 親 你 嗎
No. Can I kiss you?
我 也想 過 親 另外 一個 黑 頭髮 的 女孩 但 她 現在 有 點 麻煩
I wanted to kiss the other girl with the dark-hair, but she's in trouble.
所以 你 願意 吧 我 其實 不太 擅長
So you want to? I don't know much about kissing, though.
可以 的
Yeah.
太好了
Okay.
那 我們 ...
Okay, here we..
一 二 三
One, two, three.
你 現在 說不定 懷孕 啦
You might be pregnant now.
- 我 很 厲害 吧 - 是 啊
- Am I a good kisser? - Yeah.
我 喜歡 跳舞 你 喜歡 嗎
I love dancing. You like dancing?
我 喜歡 在 我 房間 裡 聽 著 CD 跳舞
I like dancing to my CD player in my room.
我 最愛 聽 坎 耶 · 維 斯 特 的 歌
Kanye West is my main man.
我們 把 CD 機 放 在 我 房間 裡 就 在 窗 子 邊上
We got my CD player set up in my room, right next to my window.
就 像這 樣 ...
I'm like.. Ugh..
其實 我 可以 看 你 跳舞 還可以 和 你 一起 聽 音樂
Maybe I could watch you dance and listen to music with you.
- 不行 的 我 的 CD 機 在 我 房間 裡 - 噢 也對
- No, my music is in my room. - Wow, right.
也許 ... 你 可以 偷偷 帶 我 去 啊
Maybe you could sneak me there.
你 想 耍 我 嗎 耍 我 嗎 ？
Are you trying to trick me, etc?
我 要 告 狀
I'll tell on you.
- 我 要 告發 你 - 我 會 告訴 你 一些 祕 密
- I'm telling on you! - I'll tell you something.
- 然後 你 可以 判斷 我 有 沒有 說謊 - 就 像 一場 考 試 好嗎
- And you can tell me if I'm lying or not, okay? - Like a test, okay?
我 是故 意 在 學 校 惹 事 的
I get into trouble at school on purpose.
這樣 我 就 可以 被 留 堂
So I can get sent to detention.
就 可以 避開 所有 人
To get away from everyone.
這樣 我 就 可以 獨自 一人 了
So that I can be alone.
好吧 我 可以 讓 你 看 我 房間 裡 的 東西
Okay, I'll show you something cool in my room.
好 的
Okay.
但 要 等 丹 尼斯 先生 準備 好 儀式
But after Mr. Dennis has finished to getting ready with the ritual.
我 得 走了 他 有 個 預 約
I have to go. He's got an appointment.
我 睡着 的 時候 他們 還有 一個人 會 堅持 做 醫生 囑咐 我們 的 事
When I fall sleeping, one of the others keep trying to reach what the doctor lady tell on us.
那 條褲子 上有 紅線 你 可以 看到 它 就 在 裏面
That pant, it's got a red lining. You can see it down the side.
我們 已經 聊 絲綢 和 羊毛 聊 了 二十 多 分 鐘 了
We've been talking about silk and wool blonde for 20 minutes.
你 在 深夜 給 我 發 郵 件
Can I guess that you emailed me in the middle of the night,
應該是 有 要 緊 的 事 吧
for an emergency session.
有 太多 的 問題 吧 ？
Due to variety issues...
我 已經 解決 那些 事 了 我 發了 郵 件 給 你
Aha! I was down and I emailed you. And I woke up and I feel better.
我 現在 清醒 過來 了 感覺 好多 了
I.. I feel better.
我 有 個 想法
I had a thought.
我 想 和 你 聊 聊 那 次 意外
I want to talk about the incident at work.
這 沒 什麼 的 巴 里 你 現在 很 安全
It's okay, Barry. You're safe.
我 只是 想 回顧 一下 細節 我們 只需 要 聊 聊 那些 細節
I just wanna bring the details back. We're just talk about the details.
新 澤 西 州 肯 頓 市 高 中的 學生
A high school from Camden New Jersey
到 你 工作 的 地方 做 校 外 旅行
was on a field trip at your place of work.
兩位 年輕 的 女士 走到 你 跟前
And two young ladies came up to you.
其中 一個 抓起 你的 手 伸進 衣服 裡
And one took your hand and put it under her shirt on her breast.
放到 她 的 胸口 上 另外 一位 女士 也 做了 相同 的 事
And the second did the same.
然後 他們 跑 開了 和 朋友 一起 放聲 大 笑
And then they just run off, laughing to their friends.
你 說 他們 大概是 在 玩 什麼 大 冒險
You thought that they might be on a dare.
他們 都 十七 八歲 的 樣子
You said they were 17 or 18.
而且 這 讓 你 生氣 了 好幾 天
You said it upset you for days.
我 現在 明白 了 那 就是 年輕人 的 玩 笑
It was just a teenage prank. I get that now.
這 就是 問題 所 在
And see, that's my mistake.
我 想 我 把 這 件事 想 的 太 簡單 了
I believe that I went over this incident with you too fast.
儘管 你 說你 沒事 了
Although you said, you were fine.
我 聊 過 的 別 的 人 格 都 告訴 我 沒 關係 了
And the other identities I met with said, it was fine.
但 我 相信
I believe that this...
就是 你 童 年 受辱 這 件事 給 你 帶來 了 問題
brought up issues from when you were a child and abused.
有 時候 一些 被 羞辱 的 事故
Sometimes another incident of abuse
會 促使 隱藏 的 人 格 現 身
can cause suppressed personalities to take the light.
丹 尼斯 如果 這 就是 你的 問題 所 在
Dennis, if this is you..
我 完全 能夠 理解
I completely understand..
這 就是 你 為 什麼 覺得 你 需要 出 面 來 保護 其他 人 格 的 原因
Why you felt the need to take over and protect the others.
哈哈 ... 醫生 別 再 重複 這些 了
Doctor, not this again.
其他 人 跟 我 說過 了
The others told me
你 和 帕 特 麗 夏 告訴 了 他們 怪物 的 事
that you and Patricia told the group about this beast.
我 跟 他們 說了 那 就是 丹 尼斯 和 帕 特 麗 夏
And I told them that these are just scary stories that Dennis and Patricia
編 的 恐怖 故事 來 嚇唬 他們 的
tell the others, to scare them.
那個 怪物 怎麼 能 爬 在 牆上
How this beast can crawl on walls,
就 像 最 厲害 的 攀 巖 手 以 最少 的 摩 擦
like the best rock climbers using this lightest friction and in perfections.
和 完美 的 操控 讓 自己 的 身軀 停留 在 表面
to hold his body close to seemingly sheer surfaces.
你的 面板 怎麼會 又 硬 又 厚 就 跟 犀 牛 一樣
How his skin is thick and tough, like rhinoceros.
你 真的 相信 那些 怪物 的 故事 嗎
Do you really believe the stories about the beast?
如果 真的 是 你 丹 尼斯
If this is you, Dennis,
我 明白 為 什麼 凱 文 需要 你
I understand why Kevin needs you.
你 強壯 守 紀 律 一絲 不 苟
You are strong and disciplined. You are precise.
你 不會 被 利用
And you will not be taken advantage of.
你 可以 信任 我
You can trust me.
舉 個 例子 我 可以 利用 凱 文 的 全 名
For example, I do have the ability to use Kevin's full name
來 讓 他 掌控 就 像 他 過去 那樣
and bring him forth, as he has in the past.
但 我 不會 那麼 做
But I wouldn't do that.
我 知道 那 會 讓 你們 亂 套
I know that, that would be chaos for all of you.
每個人 都 可以 主 導
Everyone would grab the light.
我 不想 傷害 你們 任何 一個人
I don't wanna hurt any of you that way.
你 不需要 隱藏
You don't have to hide.
我 知道 你 關心 凱 文
I know you are someone who cares for Kevin.
你 對於 我 來說 不是 惡 魔
You are not evil to me.
你 很 重要
You were necessary.
丹 尼斯 是 你 嗎
Dennis, is that you?
他們 一直 叫 我們 " 大 群 "
They keep calling us the horde.
就是 別 的 那些 人
The others, you know.
帕 特 麗 夏 女士 和 我 我們 總是 被 嘲笑
Mrs. Patricia and I, we're ridiculed.
我們 是 不 完美
No, we're not perfect.
但 我們 也不 至於 被 嘲笑
But, we don't deserve to be ridiculed.
我們 一直 在 抗爭 他們 必須 認識 到 這 一點
We're all struggling. They have to admit that.
很 高興 見到 你 丹 尼斯
I am pleased to meet you, Dennis.
我 也是
You, too.
你 似乎 並不 知道 是誰 因 為 緊急 事件 發 郵 件 給 我
I seemed you don't know who emailed me for the emergency session.
是 他們 中的 一個
One of the others.
- 現在 是 你 在 掌控 嗎 - 是 我們 在 掌控
- Are you in charge? - Yeah, we've taken charge.
只有 我們 可以 保護 凱 文
We're the only one who can protect Kevin.
我們 都 在 這裏 保護 凱 文
We're all here to protect Kevin.
他 太 軟弱了
He's very weak.
他 不知道 我們 可以 多 強大
He doesn't know how powerful we can be.
你 介意 跟 我 說說 你 第一次 出現 是 在 什麼 時候
Would you mind telling me, when you first came into existence?
還有 你 和 帕 特 麗 夏 那些 其他 不受 歡迎 的 人 格
And how you and Patricia,
是 怎麼 結盟 的
the other undesirable identity, became aligned?
沒 關係 你 還 是有 著 堅定 的 信念 嗎
That's okay. Do you still have strong beliefs?
- 你 說什 麼 - 怪物 的 故事
- That depends on what. - The story of the beast.
丹 尼斯 如果 你 感到 困惑 的話 有 件事 能 讓 你 明白
One thing, Dennis, that may comfort you if you are confused,
你 已經 見過 其他 人 了
is that you've met the other alters.
你們 都 在 一間 屋子 裡 坐 在 椅子 上 是嗎
You're all in a room in chairs, right?
是 的
Yeah.
但 你 從來 沒 見到 過 怪物
But you never met the beast?
因 為 他 不 和 你們 同住
Because he doesn't reside with the rest of you?
是 因 為 他 住 在 那個 火車 庭院 裡 就 像 故事 說 的
Because he resides in the train yard, as the story goes.
因 為 凱 文 的 爸爸 留 在 火車 上了
Because Kevin's dad left on the train.
但 事實 是 你 和 帕 特 麗 夏 從來 沒 見過 那個 怪物
But the fact is, you and Patricia have never met the beast.
- 對 嗎 - 是 的
- Have you? - No.
這 是 因 為 他 不是 一個人 格
That's because he's not an alter.
他 不是 第二十 個人 格
He's not the 24th identity.
他 是個 幻象
He is a fantasy.
快點 我們 走
Hurry up! Let's go!
快 啊 是 時候 了
Come on, it's time!
- 哇 噢 - 我 知道
- Wow. - I know.
- 這 是 你的 CD 機 嗎 - 對 啊
- This is your CD player? - Yeah.
你 不喜歡 ？ 它 很 舊 了
You don't like it? It's not new.
不 不 我 只是 ...
No, no, I'm just a..
我 有 點 困惑 你 說你 的 房間 有 個窗戶
I'm confused. You said it's near a window.
沒錯 在 這
Oh, that's here!
現在 它 關上 了
Now, it's closed.
又 開啟 了
Now, it's open.
又 關上 了
Now, it's closed.
又 開啟 了
Now, it's open.
你 以 為 這裏 有 個 真的 窗戶 嗎
Do you think it was a real window?
所以 你 可以 這樣 離開 ？
So you could leave, etc?
幫 我 離開 這裏 吧 海 德 薇 格
Help me get out of here, Hedwig.
只用 給 我 鑰匙 讓 我 走出 這個 門 就 行
Just give me the keys and let me out the door.
求 你 了 帕 特 麗 夏 小 姐 說過 當 怪物 來 的 時候 就 不會有 人 愚弄 我 了
Please. Ms. Patricia said that nobody'll make fun of me anymore when the beast comes.
她 說 每個人 都 會 看到 我 有 多 棒
She said that everyone must see how amazing I am.
而且 我 犯 過 的 所有 愚蠢 錯誤 他們 都 不會 在 意
And that all of my silly mistakes, they won't matter anymore.
- 我 覺得 你 還 是 快 回 你的 房間 吧 - 不
- I think you should go back to your room. - No!
等等 求 你 了 我 還想 聽 你 放 坎 耶 · 維 斯 特 的 專 輯
No, wait! Please! I wanna hear your Kanye West albums!
接着 帶 我 看看 你的 房間 我們 待 在 這 吧 不然 我 就 走了
Show me your room! Let's stay here or I'll still leave!
我 不能
I can't.
你 說 要 給 我 看 很 酷 的 東西 對 吧
You said you wanna show me something cool, right?
- 給 我 看看 - 我 不想
- Show me something! - I don't want to!
拜 託
Please!
這個
This!
- 哇 真 棒 - 這 不是 個玩具
- Wow! It's nice. - It's not a toy.
- 這 是 真的 ？ - 是 的
- Is this real? - Yes.
這 是 丹 尼斯 先生 的
It's Mr. Dennis'.
他 還不 知道 我 偷了 它 太 酷 了 對 吧
He doesn't even know I stole it. Pretty cool, right?
你 可以 聽 別人 談話 他們 甚至 不知道 你 在 聽
You can listen people talking and they don't even know you're listening.
- 誰會 談話 呢 - 別 亂 動
- Who does this talk to? - Don't touch that.
我 就 想 試試 它 能不能 用
I just want to see if it works.
嘿 別 碰 按 鈕 你 會 讓 我們 被 發現 的
Hey, don't touch the buttons. You're gonna get us found out.
我 是 文 斯 怎麼 了
Vince here, whaddup?
別說 話
Do not talk.
- 有 人嗎 - 別說 話
- What up? - Don't talk.
你 好
Hello?
別 ！
Don't!
是誰 ？
Who is this?
你 好 我 是 凱 西 · 庫 克
Hello? Hello, my name is Casey Cooke!
我 被 困 在 了 一個 地下 室 裡 我 和 另外 兩 個 女孩 被 綁架 了
I'm being held in a basement! I've been abducted with two other girls!
什麼 玩 意 ？
Who the hell is this?
有 人嗎
Hello?
凱 西 · 庫 克 我 被 綁架 了 你 得 找到 我
Casey Cooke! I've been abducted! You need to find me!
貝 蒂 是 你 嗎 這 可不 好 玩
Betty, is that you? This isn't fun.
打 給 警 察 我 離 你 很 近
Call the police! I must be near you.
我 被 困 在 一個 類似 地下 室 的 地方
I'm being held in a basement or something.
好吧 貝 蒂 聽 著 告訴 拉 里 別 鬧
Okay, Betty, listen. Tell Larry to get vicious and I...
告訴 他 我 這裏 有 他的 耳 機
Tell him I still got his own headphones.
我 不知道 我 在 哪
I don't know where I am. There is a man here.
這裏 有 個 男人 他 綁架 了 我 他 馬上 就 要 殺了 我
He abducted us and he's going to kill me.
你 還有 幾個 小時
You may have a few hours left.
求 你
Please.
求 求 你 救救 我們
I'm begging you. Somebody save us.
到底是 誰 你 是 怎麼 得到 我們 的 對 講 機 的
Who is this? And how did you get one of our walkies?
把 你的 手 擺成 懺悔 的 姿 勢 吧
Put your hands together in contrition.
在 陽光 下 我們 能 找到 我們 的 激情
" In the sun, we will find our passion. "
在 陽光 下 我們 能 找到 我們 的 目標
" In the sun, we will find our purpose. "
我 是 從 超 市 裡 一張 弔 唁 卡 上 讀 來 的
I read that on a sympathy card in the supermarket.
它 本來是 為 葬禮 準備 的 但是 我 覺得 這 話 太 美 了
It was for funerals, but I saw it was beautiful.
丹 尼斯 將會 解釋 今晚 的 意義
Dennis will explain the meaning of this evening.
怪物 是 種 嗅 覺 動物
The beast is a scenting creature,
代表 了 人類 進 化 的 最高 水 平
who represents the highest form of human evolution.
他 相信 普通人 類 的 時代 已經 結束 了
He believes the time of ordinary humanity is over.
我 希望 這 能 讓 你 感到 鎮 定
I hope this makes you feel calm.
你 將 被 ... 獻祭 給 更好 的 生物
You will be in the presents of something greater.
我 本 希望 叫 你 脫了 最後 一件 上衣 但 我 不會
I wish gonna ask you the last shirt, but I won't.
因 為 今夜 是個 神聖 的 夜晚 已經 快 要 結束 了
Because tonight is a sacred night. It's almost over.
凱 西 過來
Casey, come on!
讓 我們 假裝 我們 是 動物
Let's pretend we're animals again!
過來
Come on!
凱 西 過來 這 是 我們 的 遊 戲
Casey, come on! This is our game!
不然 我 就 跟 你 爸爸 說你 不 乖
Or I'll tell your dad you're not being nice.
過來 脫掉 你的 衣服 動物 都 不 穿衣 服
Come on! Take off your stuff. Animals don't wear clothes.
過來
Come on!
嘿 凱 西 熊
Hey, Casey-bear.
這 可不 好 玩
This isn't funny.
它 上膛 了 嗎
Is it loaded?
凱 西
Casey?
我 是 你 叔叔
I'm your uncle.
放下 凱 西
Stop it, Casey!
把 槍 放下
Put that gun down!
我 要 生氣 了
I'm getting upset!
我 會 非常 生氣
I'm about to get very angry!
你 差 點 殺了 我
You could've killed me.
" 我們 需要 你 "
" We need you. "
- 這個 地方 已經 關了 - 不 沒 關係
- This place is closed. - No, it's okay.
- 你 進 不去 的 - 沒事
- You can't get in. - No, it's okay.
你 好 丹 尼斯
Hello, Dennis.
你們 其中 一個人 剛剛 給 我 發了 郵 件
One of the others emailed me just now.
- 出 什麼 事 了 嗎 - 我們 很好
- Is everything okay? - We're fine.
丹 尼斯 凱 文 有 你 真是 太 幸運 了
Dennis, Kevin is really lucky to have you.
你們 太 特別 了 我 不想 你們 受到 傷害
You are quite extraordinary. I just don't want you guys get hurt.
你 覺得 我們 特別 嗎
You think we're extraordinary?
我 喜歡 你 丹 尼斯 我 能 進去 嗎
I like you Dennis. May I come in?
我們 談談 好嗎
And can we talk?
我 知道 你 想 告訴 我 什麼 事
I know you wanna tell me something.
爲 什麼不 直接 告訴 我 呢
Why don't you just tell me?
我們 非常 相似 你 我 都是 局 外 的 觀望 人
We're very similar, you and I. Both on the outside look and in.
請坐
Please, sit.
我 沒有 太多 拜訪 者 我 去 給 你 準備 點 水
I don't get many visitors. I'll get you some water.
他們 在 銷 售 廣 告 上 找到 一個 合適 的 住處 但是 我們 早就 住 在 這 了
They got a proper on the sales ads, but we're already here.
他們 向 我 承諾 是 真的 所以 我 就 能 擁有 它
They promoted me to make this happen, so I can have it.
你 要 去見 誰
Who are you going to meet?
我 想 談談 ... 凱 文
I want to talk about Kevin
他 媽媽 對 他 做了 什麼
and what his mother did to him.
我 都 記得
I remember the wall.
我 很 開心 你 突然 敞開 心扉
I'm happy you're suddenly so open.
凱 文 的 媽媽 曾經 給 這個 三歲 小孩 讀過 十一 個 邪惡 的 懲罰 方式
Kevin's mother had read him 11 evil ways of punishing this 3 year-old.
是 你 主 導 身體 的 時候 發生 的 嗎
Is that when you arrived in the light?
是 的
Yeah.
唯 一 避免 吸引 她 注意 的 方法 是
The one way to avoid her attention
把 所有 事情 都 做得 完美無瑕
was to keep everything spotless, everything perfect.
我 知道 你 是 出於 好意 丹 尼斯
I know you're coming from good intention, Dennis.
但是 肯定 還有 別 的 方法 可以 幫助 凱 文
But there are other ways to help Kevin now.
在 這個 系 統 下 我 失去 了 太多 病人 了
I've lost so many patients into the system.
我 想 讓 你 知道 丹 尼斯 我 永遠 都 不會 停止 為 你 鬥爭
I want you to know, Dennis. I will never stop fighting for you.
我 的 病人 就是 我 的 家人
My patients have become my family.
對 他們 我 選擇 了 有 別 於 傳統 的 方式
They, what I've chose instead of a more traditional path.
我 希望 你 能 對 我 說實話
I hope you feel you can be truly honest with me.
我 很想 跟 你 說實話
I actually wanna be honest with you.
之前 我 說謊 了 你 問 我 有 沒有 遇到 過 怪物
I lied before when you asked, if I'd ever met the beast.
我 說 " 沒有 這 並不是 真的 "
I said " no. That really isn't true.
你 寫過 一個 德 國 的 女人
You wrote about a woman in Germany,
她 已經 失明 十年 了
who'd been blind for 10 years.
然後 她 被 確 診 為 分離 性 身 份 識 別 障礙
And then, it was discovered that she had Dissociative Identity Disorder ( DID) .
她 其中 三個 人 格 發展 出了 視力
Then three of her identities developed sight.
於是 你 推 斷 她 的 信念 使 她 的 視 覺 神 經 再生 了
You speculated that her optical nerves regenerated because of her beliefs.
所以 你 想說 什麼
What are you trying to say?
總有 一些 事情
There are things, Dr. Fletcher,
我們 所有 人 都 很難 去 相信
that all of us would find hard to believe.
你 是想 告訴 我 有 第二十 種 人 格 存 在 ？
Are you trying to tell me there is a 24th identity?
是 你 保全 了 這個 人 格
You protect the broken.
就 在 你 說這 種 情況 十分 不尋常 的 時候
When you said this situation was extraordinary,
- 我 想你 也許 清楚 - 清楚 什麼
- I knew, you can maybe understand. - Understand what?
那個 怪物
The beast..
是 真實 存 在 的
is real.
他 已經 誕生 了 你 全部 說 對了
He's just emerged. You were right about everything.
他 什麼樣
What does he look like?
他 比 我 強大 多 了 而 我 是 我們 中 最強 大 的
He is much bigger than I am. And I'm the biggest of all of us.
他 很 高大 十分 強壯
He's tall, he's very muscular.
毛髮 旺盛 他的 手指 有 我們 兩倍 長
He's got a long man hair and his fingers are twice the length of ours.
他 認 為 我們 非同 尋常
He believes we're extraordinary.
我們 不 代表 錯誤 而是 無窮 的 潛 力
And we don't represent a mistake, but our potential.
你 說過 同樣 的話
You say the same things.
- 他 要 來了 - 什麼 意思
- He's on the move. - What's that mean?
我 不明 白 他 不可能 是 真的
I don't understand. He can't be real.
一個人 無論 再 怎麼 變化 也是 有 限度 的
There must be limits to what a human being can become.
這個 故事 還有 另一 部分 是嗎
And there's another whole part of the story, isn't there?
那個 關於 吞食 不潔 的 年輕人 的 部分
About the eating of the impure young?
" 不潔 " 是 什麼 意思
What does " impure" even mean?
我們 應該 好好 討論 一下 這樣 你 就 可以 很好 地 理解 了
We should discuss that, so that you can understand fully.
- 理解 什麼 - 有 時候
- Understand what? - Sometimes..
沒有 其他 的 路 可 走
There's just no other way.
你 要 去見 誰
Who are you going to meet?
他
Him.
你 知道 嗎 我 很 樂意 把 這些 都 記下來
You know what, I would love to take notes on all of this.
也許 我們 應該 在 明天 的 見面 中 好好 討論 一下
We should probably discuss this in a proper session tomorrow.
真的 嗎 你 沒 問題 嗎
Really? You're okay with this?
這 太 美妙 了 你 這麼 坦誠
This has been so wonderful, you're being so open.
我 能 看出 你的 感受 因 為 怪物 的 意念 更 強大 了
I can see that you feel very empowered by the philosophy of the beast.
我 準備 離開 了
I'm going to go now.
我 知道 你 會 理解 的 明天 見
I knew you'd understand. I'll see ya.
你 介 不 介意
Would you mind..
我 用 一下 你的 衛 生 間
If I use your bathroom?
不 就 在 樓 下 大廳 在 你 左手 邊 的 樓梯 邊上
No. It's down the hall, near the stairs on your left.
- 我 在 這 等 你 - 好 的
- I'll wait you. - Okay.
你 是誰
Who are you?
你 是誰 救救 我
Who is it? Help me.
救救 我 有 誰 在 這 兒 嗎
Help me. Is someone there?
- 噢 我 的 天 - 救救 我 求 你 了
- Oh, my God. - Please, help me!
他們 永遠 不會 發 揮 他們 的 潛 力 的
They will never reach their potential.
他們 不 重要
They don't really matter.
聽我 說 丹 尼斯
Listen to me, Dennis.
我 本 該 更 用心 傾聽 你
I should've listened better.
我 早 該 意識 到 你 多 會 假裝 自己 很 強大 了
I should've understood what you can bluffed how powerful you are.
帕 特 麗 夏 說 只要 按 著 你的 方法 做
Patricia says with your ways of working,
- 大家 就 會 明白 - 丹 尼斯
- The world will understand now. - Dennis,
這 都是 錯 的
This is wrong.
這些 年輕 姑娘 在 受苦 這 是 犯罪
These young women are suffering. This is a crime.
我 不能 讓 你 關 著 她們
I can't let you keep them here.
我們 必須 阻止 他 這個 人 格 太 可怕 了
We've got to stop this. This identity is monstrous.
你 這樣 想 我 很難 過
I'm really sad you feel this way.
你 還沒 看出 來 嗎 是 因 為 你 在 這裏 的 所作 所 為 這個 人 格 才 會 誕生
Can't you see? He is formed because of your time in this place?
這裏 有 一個 女人
There was a lady.
有 人 在 這裏
Someone's here!
我們 要 從 這裏 出去
We need to get out of these rooms!
這裏 有 什麼 東西 嗎 任何 我們 能 用 的
Is there anything in the room? Anything that we could use?
這裏 什麼 都 沒有
There's nothing in here.
這裏 有 一個 掛 鉤
There is a hanger.
謝謝你 丹 尼斯
Thank you, Dennis.
請 拿好 先生
Here you go, Sir.
我們 門外 好像是 滑 動 螺 栓
It sounded like there were slide bolts on the outside of our doors.
看看 你 能不能 通過 門 縫 移動 鎖
See if you can move the lock through the crack in the door.
" 無法 連線 到 網 絡 "
" Unable to connect to the internet"
別 慌 我們 一定 能 出去 的
Stay calm, we're getting out of here.
我們 會 救出 凱 西 的
We're gonna get Casey.
你 可以 的 瑪西亞
You can do this, Marcia.
沒錯 可以 認 為 查 哈曼 打敗 了 穆 罕 默 德
It's regarded to Chahamanas defeated Muhammad, of course.
這 場戰爭 從 一一 九 二年 持續 到一 二 〇 〇 年
The conquests between 1192-1200.
我 喜歡 默 罕 默 德 對 普 里 特 維 拉 賈 的
I would like Muhammad to present ultimatum,
最後 通 牒 " 要 麼 投降 要 麼 抵抗 "
that Prithviraj " either positize or fight" .
普 里 特 維 拉 賈 選擇 了 抵抗
Prithviraj's defines..
我們 要 勇敢 面對 大軍 來 襲 對 他們 的 恐嚇 戰術
We should stand up to the horde's advances and face up their scared tactic.
我們 應該
We should shook..
我 討厭 注 射 胰 島 素
I hate my insulin shots.
其他 人 都 沒 這 事 為 什麼 就 我 有 糖 尿 病
No one else around here has to take them. Why do I have diabetes?
所有 的 醫生 包括 弗 萊 徹 醫生
All the doctors, besides Dr. Fletcher,
都 說 我們 是 同 一個人 只是 不同 的 人 格
say that we're the same person, just personalities.
那 你們 怎麼 解釋 我 為 什麼 需要 這 玩 意 兒 操
How do you explain I'm the one who need this? You motherfuck..
在 九十 年代 我 穿着 多 袋 褲
I'm wearing cargo pants in the 90s.
再 戴 一條 圍巾 要 不是 裏面 穿 了 瓦 維 託 斯 的 T 恤
And a scarf. If it wasn't for the Varvatos t-shirt underneath,
那 可 會是 一團 糟
that'd be a mess.
我 突然 意識 到了 一些 事情
I got notice of something right now.
我 很難 過 我 覺得 我 耽誤 了 不少 時間
I'm worried sick. I have a very bad feeling that I'm losing time.
我 能 決定 誰能 主 導 對 嗎 我 覺得 有 人 趁 我 不 注意 的 時候 偷取 我 的 主 導 權
I decide who gets the light, right? I think someone is stealing the light from me when I'm not aware.
" 大 群 " 總是 迷戀 那些 " 沒有 受苦 的 人 "
The horde keep obsessing about the " ones who haven't suffered" ..
我 不知道 他們 要 做什麼
I don't know where they're going with this,
但 這 讓 我 很 害怕
but it scares me.
想 象 你 穿着 那 件 你 最 喜歡 的 醜 毛衣
Think of yourself in a couple hours at home.
躺 在家 裡 的 沙 發 上 呆 上 幾個 小時
on the couch in that ugly sweater that you love.
只是 個動物 一 有 郊 狼 之 類 的 動物 它 就 會 這麼 叫
It's an animal. He barks like this when there's a coyote or something.
凱 文 凱 文
Kev.. Kev.. Kev..
凱 文
Kev..
謝謝你 幫 我們 到 現在
Thank you for helping us till now.
凱 文 ...
Kev.. Kev..
哦 對了 我 應該 告訴 弗 萊 徹 醫生 這個 但是
And yes, I should tell Dr. Fletcher about this, but..
她 會 擔心 的 她是 一位 很好 的 女士
She'll worry. She is such a sweet woman.
我 想 我 要 出去 走走
I believe, I will go for a nice walk.
集 體 思考 一番 就 像 ...
And think this through organization, like..
這 是 我 的 週 一日 記
That's my journal for Monday.
再見
Ciao.
克 萊 爾
Claire?
瑪西亞
Marcia?
克 萊 爾 克 萊 爾 快走
Claire! Claire, let's go!
念 他的 名字
SAY HIS NAME
凱 文 · 溫 德 爾 · 克 拉 姆
Kevin Wendell Crumb.
Kevin Wendell Crumb?
凱 文 · 溫 德 爾 · 克 拉 姆
Kevin Wendell Crumb.
Kevin Wendell Crumb!
凱 文 · 溫 德 爾 · 克 拉 姆 凱 文 · 溫 德 爾 · 克 拉 姆
Kevin Wendell Crumb. Kevin Wendell Crumb.
你 弄得 一團 糟 出來 吧
You made a mess. Come out here.
凱 文 · 溫 德 爾 · 克 拉 姆 你 弄得 一團 糟
Kevin Wendell Crumb! You made a mess!
給 我 滾 出來
Get out there!
你 是誰 ？ 到底 發生 了 什麼 事
Who are you? Wha.. What's happening?
非常 恐怖 的 事情
Something horrible.
我 做了 什麼
What I do?
我 有 沒有 傷害 到 你
Did I hurt you?
弗 萊 徹 醫生 弗 萊 徹 醫生
Dr. Fletcher. Dr. Fletcher!
- 這 是誰 做 的 - 是 你
- Who did that? - You did.
我 發誓 我 剛 才 明明 在 公 交 車 上
I swear, I was on a bus.
之後 的 事情 我 都 記 不得 了
I don't remember anything after that.
今天 還 是 二 〇 一 四年 九月 十八 日 沒錯 吧
Is this still September 18,2014, right?
那裏 有 我 買 的 獵 槍
There's a shotgun I bought.
它 就 放 在 存 雜 物 的 儲 物 櫃 裡
It's in the bottom cabin that hidden behind things?
子 彈 就 放 在 外面 我 的 員 工 衣 櫃 裡
The shots are in my uniform closet, out in the service wall.
殺了 我
Kill me.
哦 冷 靜 冷 靜 別 別 那麼 做
Whoa, wait, wait, wait! No, no, don't do that!
他 接受 不來 現實
He can't handle reality.
我 是 賈 德 弗 萊 徹 醫生 收 到 我們 的 郵 件 了 吧
My name is Jade. Has Dr. Fletcher been getting our emails?
我們 必須 這麼 做 我們 得 ...
This is what we have to do. We..
我們 在 一 〇 〇 八年
Us in 1008.
當 安 納 達 帕 拉 受難 我們 目睹 他 最 崩潰 的 失敗
When Anandapala suffered to show his most crushing defeat
馬 哈 茂 德 統治 著 整個 旁 遮 普
and Mahmud overrun the entire of Punjab,
接管 著 坎 格拉 的 法 門 寺
where he's in taking the fame Temple of Kangra.
我們 一直 都 被 這個 聯盟 誤導 了
We have been wronged by this alliance, this horde of
帕 特 麗 夏 丹 尼斯 還有 那個 小 男孩 的 這 群 人
Patricia, Dennis and the boy.
他們 的 所作 所 為 不能 代表 我們
Their actions do not represent us!
大家 都 ...
Every..
大家 都 先 冷 靜 一下 ...
Everybody just take a minute!
噢 寶貝 姑娘
Oooh.. Baby girl..
他們 一直 想把 主 導 權 從 我 身上 奪走
They've been stealing control of the light from me,
不過 他們 這 群 烏 合 之 眾 得 好好 想想 辦法 了
but their group are gonna work through this.
親愛 的 我 是 巴 里
Honey, my name is Barry.
你 真 不應該 用 對 講 機 的
You shouldn't've used the walkie talkie.
我們 差 點 被 抓 了
They almost caught us.
停下 海 德 薇 格
Stop it, Hedwig!
你 從來 就 沒 做對 過 看看 你 自己 你 在 搖 籃 中 發抖
You never right. Look at you! You're so afraid in the bud.
就是 因 為 我 丹 尼斯 和 帕 特 麗 夏 才 會 掌管 這 一切
Dennis and Mrs. Patricia are in charge because of me!
我 要 把 主 導 權 交給 他們 了
I'm gonna give the light to them now.
從 今 以後 再 沒人 敢 嘲笑 我
No one is allow to make fun of me anymore!
謝謝你 海 德 薇 格
Thank you, Hedwig.
- 一切 都 沒事 了 - 凱 文 · 溫 德 爾 · 克 拉 姆
- Everything's fine now. - Kevin Wendell Crumb.
凱 文 睡着了 我們 讓 他 一直 沉睡 著 吧
Kevin is asleep. We've made him sleep far away.
你 可以 一 整 晚 都 叫 他的 名字 親愛 的
You can call his name all your night, dear bird,
只可 惜 他 聽 不 見 了
but he's not going to hear you.
怪物 就 在 我們 中間 他 夢想 著 能有 一個 更大 的 群 體 才能 約束 住 他
The beast has shed with us his dreams of a larger group to sustain him.
下次 會有 十 到 十二 個 毫無 價值 的 年輕人
Ten to twelve unworthy young next time.
這 只不過是 開始
This is just the start!
放手
Let go!
不
Oh, my God!
救我
Help me!
救救 我
Help! Help! Help!
這 病 在家 族 裡 實施 流傳 我 爸爸 也是 這麼 死掉 的
It runs in our family. My daddy died, too.
都是 一樣 突發 心臟 病
Same way, heart attack.
不過 你 不必 擔心 我 會 好好 照顧 你的
But you don't need to worry. I'm going to take care of you.
噢 ... 你 也不 會 給 我 添 麻煩 的 對 吧
Well, you won't be given me any trouble, will you?
我 知道 你 不會 的 親愛 的
I know you won't, sweety.
我們 無比 光榮
We are glorious!
我們 無所畏懼
We will no longer be afraid!
只有 飽受 痛苦
Only through pain..
你 能 實現 你 偉大 的 目標 嗎
can you achieve your greatness!
不純 潔 的 東西 無法 觸控
The impure are the untouched,
無法 點燃 無法 被殺 死
the unburned, the unslain!
那些 還未 分裂 的 人
Those who have not been torn,
沒有 體現 他們 的 價值
have no value in themselves,
在 這個 世界上 無 一 席 之地
and no place in this world!
他們 沉睡 著
They are asleep!
你的 槍 傷 不了 我
Your gun cannot hurt me.
難道 你 看不出來 嗎 我 不是 人類
Can't you see? I am not human.
凱 文 是 人 但 我 更高 級
Kevin is a man. I am much more.
你 和 其他 人 不 一樣
You are different from the rest.
你的 心靈 很 純潔
Your heart is pure.
太 棒 了
Rejoice!
受過 苦難 的 人更 強大
The broken are the more evolved!
太 棒 了
Rejoice!
以 瑪 麗 約瑟 夫 的 名義
What in the name of Mary-Joseph!
你 在 這 兒 幹 什麼
What are you doing in this area?
繼續 走 親愛 的 他們 不會 傷害 你的
Just keep walking, honey. They won't do nothing.
文 斯 報 警
Vince, call the police!
她 說 在 這 片 維護 區域 下面 有 人 受傷 了
She said some people got hurt in the area below maintenance.
好 的
Okay.
我 要 對 你 做 一下 檢查
I'm just gonna check you.
第三 個 死者 是 凱 倫 · 弗 萊 徹 博士
The third deceased name of Dr. Karen Fletcher.
還 在 努力 尋找 她 的 家人
Still trying to look out her family.
凱 西 · 庫 克 的 監護人 來了
Casey Cooke's guardian's here.
你 叔叔 來了
You uncle's here.
準備 好 走了 嗎
You ready to go?
接下來 怎麼辦
And then no through.
我們 是誰 取決於 我們 怎麼 想
We are what we believe we are.
天 吶 酷 斃 了
Holy shit! This is so cool!
他們 現在 該 相信 我們 是 存 在 的 了 吧
They're gonna believe we exist now, right?
他們 必須 相信
They gotta have to.
那麼 接下來 我們 幹 什麼
So, what are we do now?
我們 要 相信 他 他 會 保護 我們 的
We trust in him. He'll protect us.
看看 他 能做 什麼
Look, what he can do.
讓 他 給世 界 看看 我們 的 力量
Let him show the world how powerful we can be.
嫌 疑 犯 凱 文 · 克 拉 姆
The suspected murderer, Kevin Crumb,
受 極具 爭議 的 多 重 人 格 的 心 理 障礙 影響
suffers from the controversial psychological disorder, DID.
這個 事件 中的 傳言 簡直 難以置信
The rumors coming out of the scene almost unbelievable.
關於 嫌 疑 人 在 連續 捱 了 兩 槍 之後
There are conflicting stories if the suspect is alive or dead
是否 還 活着 說法 不 一
after sustaining 2 point length gunshot.
報告 顯示 他 其中 一個人 格
Reports even indicate one of his personality
是 多 種 動物 的 混合 體 這些 動物 正 來自 於 他 工作 的 費 城 動物 園
is an amalgam of various animals in the Philadelphia Zoo, where he worked.
媒 體 已經 給 這個 攻擊 者 起了 一個 外 號
The press is already referring to the alleged attacker by a dork name,
據 知情 人 透露
leaked by a source close to the case.
因 為 他的 多 重 人 格 他 被 媒 體 稱 為 " 大 群 "
Because of his many personalities, he is being called " The Horde" .
就 像 他們 十五 年前 遺忘 的 那個 坐 在 輪 椅 上 的 瘋子 一樣
This is like that crazy guy in the wheelchair that they put away 15 years ago.
他們 也 給 他 起了 個 好 玩 的 名字
And he gave him a funny name, too.
是 什麼 來 著
What was it?
- 玻璃 先生 - 噢 對
- Mr. Glass. - Oh, yeah.